<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on mokdarren</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on mokdarren</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 16:40:10 +0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mid month algo update</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/trading/mid_month_update/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Jul 2020 16:40:10 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/trading/mid_month_update/</guid>
      <description>Greetings fellow traders,
Time for a mid-month update of the flush algo-trader. Over the past 2 weeks, we achieved an ROI of 6.19% with a total of 11 trades. Once again, if anyone is keen to follow the progress of this script: https://bit.ly/2ZBIAQv
If you have noticed I have been trading exclusively on Brent Crude Oil the past 2 weeks and this is because the backtests I have performed showed that this strategy works exceptionally well on this derivative.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flush Algo 100% win rate</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/trading/performance_tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2020 14:35:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/trading/performance_tracking/</guid>
      <description>Greetings fellow traders,
We achieved a 100% win rate with three winning trades, and we&amp;rsquo;re up 4.5% in just three days. This Flush Algo took me close to 1 month to backtest and develop and I&amp;rsquo;m glad it&amp;rsquo;s showing good potential! I will be updating the Algo&amp;rsquo;s performance in this google spreadsheet: https://bit.ly/2ZBIAQv
It&amp;rsquo;s looking pretty good being up 4.5%, but it&amp;rsquo;s hard to tell it&amp;rsquo;s long-term performance with a sample size of 3 trades.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trading Alogrithmically, powered by OANDA</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/trading/flush/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 20:18:13 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/trading/flush/</guid>
      <description>This entry will mark the start of running a live algorithm on OANDA, I will document it&#39;s performance weekly on this blog to determine it&#39;s profitability. I call this strategy the Flush strategy, and it makes trades when a significant move is felt in the market. After performing backtests on 2 years of past data, I found this strategy to be highly profitable on volatile markets such as Crude Oil and Gold.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beggining with the end in mind</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jul 2020 15:50:28 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/first-post/</guid>
      <description>COVID19 has not only shortened my dreamy 6-month long study abroad program in Sweden but also caused my internship at a reputable bank to be canceled. As Parkinson&#39;s Second Law puts it, &#34;work expands to fill the time available for its completion&#34;. I had to do something about it to make my time productive. I never had the opportunity to explore Web technologies outside of my Academic Work in NUS. Therefore this was a good opportunity to explore the field of Web Development.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
